▍2026 辛辛那提 WTA1000 女单半决赛
佩古拉 7-5 4-6 6-4 斯瓦泰克 · 赛后采访
I've said and maybe mentioned
这话我以前可能也说过
before, but my coach and I have this thing
我和教练之间有个说法
where we say it's just practice.
就说这只是训练
And so we kind of I kind of tell myself
所以比赛打到一半时
that in the middle of the match
我也会这样告诉自己
because at the end
因为归根结底
of the day like I'm working on things
我一直都在练一些东西
and I know how I need to play
也知道自己该怎么打
and I practice that all the time in practice,
平时训练里一直这么练
but when I come out here
真正来到赛场上
it's the same thing and next week it's going
其实也是同一回事 下周
to be the same thing and when I go
还是同一回事 到亚洲赛季
to Asia it's going to be the same thing.
也还是同一回事
Like every single week it's the same story.
每一周其实都一样
So I just told myself to kind
所以我只告诉自己
of be brave, and I—like—the only way I
要勇敢一点 因为我知道
was going to win was if I play a certain way.
只有那样打才可能赢
I'm not going to win
如果我退到
if I'm 10 ft behind the baseline
底线后十英尺
and letting her push me around.
任由她压着我打 我赢不了
Like yeah, sometimes
当然 有时候
if I have to dig out a point, of course,
为了救下一分
like that one point I'll do it,
比如刚才那一分 我会去拼
but I really have to impose taking away
但整体上我必须打出压迫感
time away from her and I know we've
抢走她的时间 这正是
been working on that a lot.
我们一直在练的
So I just had to trust kind of just getting
所以我只能相信这些
my footwork a little bit sharper,
让脚下移动再敏捷一点
looking to take the ball early
争取更早击球
and doing what I know I
做我知道自己能做到的事
can do and it just happened to work today.
真正做出来 今天刚好奏效了
So you still have a quick turnaround
离决赛很近 恢复时间依然很短
before the final and you've shared
你之前也跟我们分享过
with us what that looks like day
决赛前一天通常
before before you get ready for a final,
会怎么准备
but I'm curious between the last one
但我更想知道 从上一场
and here you had that medical timeout
到今天 你经历了医疗暂停
and we were hoping you'd
我们当然都希望你
be completely healthy.
已经完全恢复
We weren't sure until you stepped out
可在你上场前
there.
我们也无法确定
You obviously look great.
今天你的状态显然很好
Yeah.
对
What did that day and a half look like?
这一天半你是怎么过的
Were you Did you have to do anything extra
为了确保身体没问题
to make sure you were healthy?
有额外做什么吗
Nothing.
什么都没做
Zero. Yeah,
零 完全没有
I mean I got like a little treatment,
就是做了点简单治疗
but I did nothing.
但除此之外什么都没干
Laid out by the pool.
躺在泳池边晒太阳
I have a pool
我家里有泳池
That's the key.
这就是秘诀
house.
就在家里
That's the key.
这才是秘诀
And I just like got some vitamin D
然后就晒晒太阳 补点维生素D
and I literally did nothing.
我真的什么都没做
No. No, no.
没有 真的没有
I didn't come to site at all.
我完全没来比赛场地
I've done that like a few times here
我以前也有几次这样
and there—maybe Miami—when I'm really
有时确实会这样 比如迈阿密
when I was coming off playing a lot
那次我之前已经打了很多
of really, like, long day matches,
又漫长又辛苦的比赛
I just won't come to site.
我就干脆不来场地
Yeah, my coaches love
对 我的教练特别喜欢这样
when I cuz I'm like kind
因为我在训练上
of a practice like perfectionist.
有点完美主义
So they just love it
所以对他们来说
when I'm totally not motivated
他们就喜欢看到我完全
to go to the site,
不想来场地训练
they're really happy because they know
他们反而高兴 因为知道
that I'm in like a good place mentally
我的心理状态很好
where I don't feel like I have to overdo it.
不会觉得自己非得练过头
I think coming off of Amanda's match
我想打完和阿曼达的那场
with a little bit of an injury
身上又有点伤
that I wasn't sure how I was going
我也不确定
to recover, forced me to do that.
不知能否恢复 反而逼我休息
So, they were kind of happy about that.
所以他们还挺开心的
She's got a sunshine glow about her.
她整个人都晒出了阳光感